

POUYA KHAST

ABOUT ME

Passionate full stack web developer with great experience in the field using most popular and modern technologies such as Ruby on Rails,
Java-script, bootstrap. Great communication skills and the ability to work both solo and in group.
Highly motivated and able to learn new things fast.

PERSONAL INFO

*

DATE OF BIRTH 12.07.1988



ADDRESS

Kungshallsvägen 3, lgh3, 382 43 Nybro Sweden



PHONE 0736375611



E-MAIL pouyakhast@gmail.com



Bachelor degree of computer science

EDUCATION

Linnaeus university

PERSONAL SKILLS

WEB TECHNOLOGIES

RUBY ON RAILS

RUBY

JAVA

SQL

SASS

JS

JQUERY

NODE.JS

EXPRESS.JS

HTML/CSS

HTML5/CSS 3

BOOTSTRAP

https://github.com/PouyaKhast



JOB EXPERIENCE

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

FREELANCE

MAR 2016- CURRENT

I am implementing and designing web projects with different web technologies for my clients.

FRONT END/BACKE END DEVELOPER JUNE 2015- SEP 2015

LONDARK

Design and implementation of Londark company web page using ruby on rails and bootstrap.

FRONT END DEVELOPER

JUNE 2013- SEP 2013

KNOWLDGEGE TECHNOLOGY AREA (KTE)

Part of front end team working with html css and jquery to create their website.

•••

LANGUAGES

INTERESTS



REFERENCES

1

PLAY GUITAR





READ BOOKS



BASKETBALL

CEO OF KNOWLEGE TECHNOLOGY AREA.(KTE)

Seyed Majid Quraie info@kte.ir

+9821 885 33 266

HEAD OF COMPUTER SCIENCE DEPARTMENT

Ola Flygt ola.flygt@lnu.se 047070 8649